{"sid": "UKSJNABCOVPM_main", "calc_equals_delay": 3, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 342547, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 342548, "question": "63+13", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 345576]], "time_left_end": "297", "answered_time": 345576, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "297", "question_time_start": 345577, "question": "78+37+23+47", "correct_answer": 185, "events": [["submit", 355385]], "time_left_end": "288", "answered_time": 355385, "user_answer": "185", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "288", "question_time_start": 355385, "question": "8+98+77", "correct_answer": 183, "events": [["submit", 363201]], "time_left_end": "280", "answered_time": 363201, "user_answer": "183", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "280", "question_time_start": 363201, "question": "4+24+17", "correct_answer": 45, "events": [["submit", 370568]], "time_left_end": "272", "answered_time": 370568, "user_answer": "45", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "272", "question_time_start": 370568, "question": "4+3+6+13", "correct_answer": 26, "events": [["submit", 375687]], "time_left_end": "267", "answered_time": 375687, "user_answer": "26", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "267", "question_time_start": 375687, "question": "24+516", "correct_answer": 540, "events": [["submit", 380293]], "time_left_end": "263", "answered_time": 380293, "user_answer": "540", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "263", "question_time_start": 380294, "question": "6+7+7+43", "correct_answer": 63, "events": [["submit", 384241]], "time_left_end": "259", "answered_time": 384241, "user_answer": "63", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "259", "question_time_start": 384241, "question": "34+873", "correct_answer": 907, "events": [["submit", 392145]], "time_left_end": "251", "answered_time": 392144, "user_answer": "907", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "251", "question_time_start": 392145, "question": "7+68+83", "correct_answer": 158, "events": [["submit", 399985]], "time_left_end": "243", "answered_time": 399985, "user_answer": "158", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "243", "question_time_start": 399986, "question": "49+18", "correct_answer": 67, "events": [["submit", 403541]], "time_left_end": "239", "answered_time": 403541, "user_answer": "67", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 403541, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "239", "question_time_start": 403541, "question": "3+19+87", "correct_answer": 109, "events": [["submit", 409253]], "time_left_end": "234", "answered_time": 409253, "user_answer": "109", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "234", "question_time_start": 409254, "question": "3+88+77", "correct_answer": 168, "events": [["submit", 416020]], "time_left_end": "227", "answered_time": 416020, "user_answer": "168", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "227", "question_time_start": 416020, "question": "67+28", "correct_answer": 95, "events": [["submit", 419768]], "time_left_end": "223", "answered_time": 419768, "user_answer": "95", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "223", "question_time_start": 419769, "question": "83+948", "correct_answer": 1031, "events": [["submit", 429485]], "time_left_end": "214", "answered_time": 429485, "user_answer": "1031", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "214", "question_time_start": 429485, "question": "9+7+3+79", "correct_answer": 98, "events": [["submit", 435196]], "time_left_end": "208", "answered_time": 435196, "user_answer": "98", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "208", "question_time_start": 435196, "question": "38+249", "correct_answer": 287, "events": [["submit", 441050]], "time_left_end": "202", "answered_time": 441050, "user_answer": "287", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "202", "question_time_start": 441050, "question": "7+29+46", "correct_answer": 82, "events": [["submit", 449784]], "time_left_end": "193", "answered_time": 449784, "user_answer": "82", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "193", "question_time_start": 449785, "question": "6+7+3+57", "correct_answer": 73, "events": [["submit", 458351]], "time_left_end": "185", "answered_time": 458351, "user_answer": "73", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "185", "question_time_start": 458351, "question": "74+13+69+76", "correct_answer": 232, "events": [["submit", 470557]], "time_left_end": "172", "answered_time": 470557, "user_answer": "232", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "172", "question_time_start": 470557, "question": "98+86", "correct_answer": 184, "events": [["submit", 475751]], "time_left_end": "167", "answered_time": 475750, "user_answer": "184", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 475751, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "167", "question_time_start": 475751, "question": "8+4+4+49", "correct_answer": 65, "events": [["submit", 481006]], "time_left_end": "162", "answered_time": 481006, "user_answer": "65", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "162", "question_time_start": 481006, "question": "6+44+36", "correct_answer": 86, "events": [["submit", 485538]], "time_left_end": "157", "answered_time": 485538, "user_answer": "86", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "157", "question_time_start": 485538, "question": "9+8+3+29", "correct_answer": 49, "events": [["submit", 492569]], "time_left_end": "150", "answered_time": 492569, "user_answer": "49", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "150", "question_time_start": 492570, "question": "7+48+19", "correct_answer": 74, "events": [["submit", 501569]], "time_left_end": "141", "answered_time": 501569, "user_answer": "64", "user_correct": "False", "score": "22"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "141", "question_time_start": 501569, "question": "96+393", "correct_answer": 489, "events": [["submit", 509456]], "time_left_end": "134", "answered_time": 509456, "user_answer": "489", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "134", "question_time_start": 509456, "question": "67+67+98+49", "correct_answer": 281, "events": [["submit", 523835]], "time_left_end": "119", "answered_time": 523835, "user_answer": "281", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "119", "question_time_start": 523835, "question": "33+44", "correct_answer": 77, "events": [["submit", 527449]], "time_left_end": "116", "answered_time": 527449, "user_answer": "77", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "116", "question_time_start": 527449, "question": "39+334", "correct_answer": 373, "events": [["submit", 537570]], "time_left_end": "105", "answered_time": 537570, "user_answer": "373", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "105", "question_time_start": 537571, "question": "4+69+49", "correct_answer": 122, "events": [["submit", 544456]], "time_left_end": "99", "answered_time": 544456, "user_answer": "122", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "99", "question_time_start": 544457, "question": "83+93", "correct_answer": 176, "events": [["submit", 547415]], "time_left_end": "96", "answered_time": 547414, "user_answer": "176", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 547415, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "96", "question_time_start": 547415, "question": "8+13+39", "correct_answer": 60, "events": [["submit", 552536]], "time_left_end": "91", "answered_time": 552536, "user_answer": "60", "user_correct": "True", "score": "29"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "91", "question_time_start": 552536, "question": "9+9+4+68", "correct_answer": 90, "events": [["submit", 558580]], "time_left_end": "84", "answered_time": 558580, "user_answer": "90", "user_correct": "True", "score": "30"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "84", "question_time_start": 558580, "question": "89+38", "correct_answer": 127, "events": [["submit", 566284]], "time_left_end": "77", "answered_time": 566284, "user_answer": "127", "user_correct": "True", "score": "31"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "77", "question_time_start": 566285, "question": "26+617", "correct_answer": 643, "events": [["submit", 571600]], "time_left_end": "71", "answered_time": 571600, "user_answer": "643", "user_correct": "True", "score": "32"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "71", "question_time_start": 571601, "question": "8+18+46", "correct_answer": 72, "events": [["submit", 577190]], "time_left_end": "66", "answered_time": 577190, "user_answer": "92", "user_correct": "False", "score": "31"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "66", "question_time_start": 577190, "question": "7+9+8+69", "correct_answer": 93, "events": [["submit", 586548]], "time_left_end": "56", "answered_time": 586548, "user_answer": "93", "user_correct": "True", "score": "32"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "56", "question_time_start": 586548, "question": "18+778", "correct_answer": 796, "events": [["submit", 592857]], "time_left_end": "50", "answered_time": 592857, "user_answer": "798", "user_correct": "False", "score": "31"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "50", "question_time_start": 592857, "question": "58+69+78+64", "correct_answer": 269, "events": [["submit", 608963]], "time_left_end": "34", "answered_time": 608963, "user_answer": "269", "user_correct": "True", "score": "32"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "34", "question_time_start": 608963, "question": "8+96+73", "correct_answer": 177, "events": [["submit", 614486]], "time_left_end": "29", "answered_time": 614486, "user_answer": "177", "user_correct": "True", "score": "33"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "29", "question_time_start": 614487, "question": "53+46", "correct_answer": 99, "events": [["submit", 617640]], "time_left_end": "25", "answered_time": 617640, "user_answer": "99", "user_correct": "True", "score": "34"}}}, "block_4": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 617640, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "25", "question_time_start": 617640, "question": "9+8+7+56", "correct_answer": 80, "events": [["submit", 629815]], "time_left_end": "13", "answered_time": 629815, "user_answer": "80", "user_correct": "True", "score": "35"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "13", "question_time_start": 629815, "question": "3+3+6+47", "correct_answer": 59, "events": [["submit", 634414]], "time_left_end": "9", "answered_time": 634414, "user_answer": "59", "user_correct": "True", "score": "36"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "9", "question_time_start": 634414, "question": "6+53+59", "correct_answer": 118, "events": [["submit", 638880]], "time_left_end": "4", "answered_time": 638880, "user_answer": "118", "user_correct": "True", "score": "37"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "4", "question_time_start": 638881, "question": "66+46+79+77", "correct_answer": 268, "events": []}}}}}